[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Come stai?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Bongiorno.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "It look like the worst food you can eat right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "It looks like stuff that were pile on the punt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "What was the total calorie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Let's see if the audience can guess how many calories in all of this food, six meals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Tangerine (ph) how many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "500.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Andre (ph) how many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "2,500.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "That's my favorite Italian dish and normally you consume a lot of calories, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well normally the pasta is made with flour which is almost 300 calories in and of itself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "How many calories?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "OK, so that would be about 710, it's now 190 calories carb-free.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "How do you culturally change that kind of thinking and the fast food epidemic and so on to get them to start to cook at home in a way that can produce this kind of result?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "It's an unbelievably difficult question to answer, but I think what we're doing right now is part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Do you have better sex on your food Rocco?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I'll tell you one of the reasons I got healthy is because my sex wasn't as good as it should be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Let me get to this, one question so how old are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", ",", "CD", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "I'm 46 years old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "''"], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Two years difference, you're 6'1\" right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "6'1\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "You were at your heaviest how much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Almost 230.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "And you lost how much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Forty pounds and so, if a chubby chef with a crooked spine and flat feet who could totally get away with it by the way, it's not like girls weren't attracted to me or anything if there was any downside other than the health.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "I'm doing great, Piers how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "So you're this unknown guy who just announced he'd been eating a lot of subways and lost a lot of weight and before we know it subway business was completely transformed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Do you still eat subway sandwiches?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I do, you know, I don't eat it every single day anymore but I've learned, you know, exactly in moderation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "RB", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "What were you at your heaviest, what are you now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Piers, my heaviest I was 320, right now today I got on a scale this morning in the hotel in L.A. I'm 240.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "And how do you this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "So, what -- I was like a business guy running around the world, doing deals, focused on, you know, building companies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "How have you managed to stay so disciplined?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Sure, well the first thing I'd say Piers is I didn't look at what I did as I diet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "What you want to become me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "I don't know about so much you, but I thought like I need a different perspective.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "So that's you on the left before, that's what you became in the middle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Yes six months.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "So, I mean quite extraordinary, that's a six month period?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Six months, yeah, so a year long.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Because you'd never been fat right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Never been overweight, never struggled.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "JJR", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "So what were the key takeaways for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "The biggest things I learned was more so on the mental and emotional side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Did you suddenly find that, that wasn't happening if you lost it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "I think some people looked at me differently, I could see the stares at the grocery store loading up my cart with soda and cereal but no one ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJR", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Oh, Drew loved it, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "No, no one was really mean, but I felt like for my perspective people were staring at me more, so my self esteem, my confidence levels took a hit the bigger I got and so that's the hard part to deal with, lose my self esteem being out in public or getting out of the shower covering up in front of my wife, that's how it affected me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "What was the point when you went -- how heavy were you when you had enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "14 stone, 14 stone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Was there a moment or kind of self awareness where you went OK that's enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I just felt like where was it going to end.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "How do we change the thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I have heard so often people trying to blame people for this problem and I will grant you one moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "You have seen those and have treated people with those, when it gets to that stage people are pretty desperate aren't they to do something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well our whole country is desperate, so they're desperate but for sure I think it's important to understand this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Let's do something about it, and he lost, let me ask the audiences, we got to answer this, I want to ask you two questions, the first one is, do you think super sized sodas are good for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "But you don't want to be told you can't have it, how do we get through this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "But the reality of it is, it's making you sick, whether you have weight problem or not, so stop to think about that for a minute.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["France"]}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "A big issue in the sense if you just did half an hour of brisk walking a day, a lot of doctors tell me that that coupled with a reasonable diet is more than enough to exercise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "It can't hurt but look, you're going to have to be on Tour de France in order, you know, amass the kind of calorie burning that you're going to need to compensate for the kind of over consumption that you can be led.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 396, "question": "So diet is the key?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Yeah, controlling the intake especially with ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Tracy, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I'm great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "So every time I see one of these celebrities having a baby within about three months they look like a stick ends yet again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "What you do to these poor women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "You know what I support them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "I think we gave them -- didn't we give them DVD?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Well, that's a little surprise there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "What are the key things that women who've had a baby need to do quite quickly to get rid of the baby fat and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Well, right now Kim is doing what she should be doing which is bonding with her baby.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "What is it about your Barry's Bootcamp is different to others?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Can you get properly fit by -- or just doing weights or just doing running is the best combination, both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What is it and how does it work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "It's indoor cycling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Josh, you actually did the Shaun T Insanity thing and it worked, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Yes, it did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Shaun T Insanity"], "PERSON": ["Josh"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "What did you end up, the weight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "I started at 293 and was down to 203.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "And what is unique about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "What's unique about it is that, you know, well first of all I'd like to say that people are afraid to workout with me because they think it's so hard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "What is a modifier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "A modifier is so and so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "So it's a less of Shaun T basically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Yes, kind of.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Shaun T"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Barry, do you think as a workout, how many times a week to get reasonably fit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "That's a good question because I'm believer in the hour workout.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "And how many days a week would you recommend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Oh, five days a week.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Barry, you want to go free flagging while you're at it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "You know, if I can also say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "So this is like a bike, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "It's a bike.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Then what happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I want you to look at that little screen and I want you to take your torque to 25.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "This one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Until it gets to 25.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "That's our word for resistance torque, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "ORGAN: OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "So you're at 25, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "You're good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Easy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "How's that going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "This is, you know, getting a little testing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Should we try 30?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Why not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "So is that a good balance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "That's very good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "And how many seconds do I have to keep doing this for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "About 30.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]